









# Hà Duy Hưng

Mobile App Developer

Follow





### Introduction

■ Email: mr.haduyhung@gmail.com

Phone: +84389927354

Gender: Male

mate of birth: **April 15, 1990** 

Address: Hanoi, Vietnam

i Professional Summary:

Talented full-stack Mobile App Developer with seven years of software and mobile development experience in a broad range of industries, financial technology, music entertainment, computer vision and education technology. Able to work well in both of Android and iOS platform. Highly skilled in troubleshooting, solution researching, and new technology integration.

## **Skills**

Language: English

Programming Language: Java, Swift, Objective-C, Dart

Framework & Tool: Android (5+ years), iOS (2+ years),

Flutter (3 years)

#### **Interests**

Reading, Football, Gaming, Meditation

# **Additional Information**

Github: https://github.com/hnvn

## Work experience



🖶 **B-Gate**, Game developer

APR 2012 - DEC 2014

- Build cross-platform mobile games on Android and iOS.
- Research and implement solutions for the real-time online game, include client-server protocol communication, connection module on the client side.



**NextTech**, Android developer

APR 2015 - JUN 2017

- Build e-wallet mobile application on Android (Vimo).
- Work on OpenCV framework to build KYC module to detect, track and recognize human-identity on Android and iOS platform (Verime).



**Bibomart**, Mobile app developer

OCT 2017 - OCT 2018

- Build e-commerce mobile application using Flutter framework.



Sendo, Senior mobile app developer

NOV 2018 - APR 2020

- Build e-wallet mobile application using Flutter framework (Senpay).
- Integrate e-wallet module built on Flutter into existing native application (Sendo).

#### **Education**



Hanoi University of Science and Technology, The degree of

Engineer in Information Technology

SEP 2008 - JUN 2011

Diploma: Good